Good morning, ma'am.
You came to visit?
We're going to Jet Pose together.
There's a lot of people here.
What's that?
You look like a celebrity.
What's this?
This is so much fun!
I'm wearing a yellow towel from a penlight, so I'm with all the Mision people.
Look at the three of you, all to yourselves now.
Let's go.
Okay.
All right.
That's the first time I've said it.
Yes, I have.
Cheese.
Yes, cheese.
OK.
Thank you.
I want to see something.
You're going to do it unexpectedly.
What?
I want to come in.
May I?
Please hold this.
I'm coming.
On the side.
Okay.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Oh, man.
I'm so happy.
I'm happy, I'm happy.
I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
Wow, I feel like I'm taking pictures at Univa. Wow, I feel like I'm taking pictures at Univa.
Univa.
This is Univa.
This is Univa
Enzytex!
Are you quitting?
No.
Thank you.
That's great.
Whew!
There's more.
Yeah.
I was so surprised.
The guests on the bottom side, please look at them.
Yes, I'm here.
Thank you very much,
Please raise the tension.
Let's go.
Good luck.
Good luck and best regards.
When I say equal, can I say love?
Okay, I'll go. I'm going.
Okay,
Equal love!
Thank you for your time.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much for watching.
Now I'd like to move on to the next song.
Please listen to it.
I have to joke all the time
In a blot of glitter
Wear a dress
It's always funny
Always funny It's always been funny.
If it becomes funny...
I thought I could just...
I thought it would just happen.
It's a game.
It was a game.
I cuted this tooth.
Cuted
Kara Volume is
Love chew on this world
Love chew
is it so
But
I like the sound.
I like it.
Hi, Mr. Finch.
Stay here
Come on, get on the bear
The last night is
difícil
Let's try it on
I feel sadness.
I mustn't.
iron and night
Glass gry
So
Wind far
большой
With ease
Light
éti
chi
is
and
light
day
ron ron
to
IF
Are you doing well?
Keep up the good work and have fun with your mistakes!
I have a lot of hair.
I've got a really cute mono pasta with a lot of feeling.
Even the stun back is looking cool.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
On a high course, I'll fit in with the sofar
On the locomise train, your world's about to change
Hey, be a princess
If you let my fluffy hands make love to you
If I could dream
I'd be a nice, sweet human
Just the job I've been waiting for
Now's the time to be happy
Fighting Heroine Icon Love
Today is a special venue until the menu!
Call with me.
Who do you like?
Risa.
Elle Fan
Mr. Pukimon.
Artie.
Arkzin
Futake
Hoya Hoya
Hanaratsuda
Yay!
Protect me, I'm in trouble
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know.
Strong, sweet, and just sweet.
Manaratsudaka
To love, fist from you, exercise
Trust in the world
Believe in me, girl
Start Getting Started
I want to be a princess.
Come on, let's ride around Shibuya on a white horse
Let's run around
Feel the travelers
Aim for the target
Kiss me and I'll save you
Wake up, wake up, wake up
Just a thumb's breadth away
I'm up there.
War Heroine Ikon Love
War heroine Ikon love
War heroine icon love
War heroine
Ikonlove
Yes, three special guests, Elmo, Cookie Monster and Abby came to visit us.
They were so cute.
And they were so sharp.
It was really amazing.
They were so cool.
Amazing.
You are the best.
Thank you so much for putting on a great show with us.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
Look at that. Your hair is amazing.
It's amazing.
Well, Kihara, how was your day?
I thought it might be a little cold today,
I thought it would be cold today, but it was so hot, and it's already spring, uniballoon, spring has come already.
It was so beautiful, like the cherry blossoms, and it was a great memory for me.
Did you all have a good time?
It was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
How was Miryan?
It was a lot of fun.
I really enjoyed dancing with everyone, and dancing with all the characters,
It was an experience of a lifetime.
It was wonderful. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Well, our riser ends here, but I am sure everyone is still looking back on their youth.
Please enjoy yourselves to the end. Thank you very much for your time today.
That's all for now. Thank you very much.
It's so warm!
Thank you for your hard work. It was fun.
It was fun.
It was so hot I thought it was summer
Thank you for your hard work.
That was fast.
It was fun.
I'm going to play a lot more.
Bye bye.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you! Thanks for your hard work!
I was really happy.
Wow!
That's great!
Oh my God, I might have been whispered to.
A lot!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Wow!
Okay, I'm going.
OK, I'm going.
I'm going.
I'm filming.
I'll do the last one on the next turn.
Three, two, one.
I'm filming.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Cover my heart
Perfect!
Thank you.
You scared me.
Girl
Bye-bye.
Ah!
Elfar.
So, Unival 2024 is over! Thank you to everyone who came and supported us!
We had always said that it would be great if we could do a live performance at USJ someday, so we were really happy to be able to perform on stage this time!
Thank you very much.
I also had the opportunity to dance with the Sesame Street group, which really made me feel at home.
We had rehearsals from early in the morning, and thanks to all the characters, we were full of energy from the morning, and we had a great time during the performance.
We were so happy to see so many fans in front of us, to our right and to our left.
And even though it was in a different place than usual...
I think we were able to create a unique live performance in the same space as usual, even though it was in a different place than usual.
We performed 13 songs in one hour.
I think we had a very equal relationship with the fans, as they were all very vocal and excited to see us, and they followed us.
After the show, we would like to play with them as well.
I hope you all have a great time at Unival.
I hope everyone will practice hard and go home with lots of memories.
Thank you very much for your time today.